[
    {
        "Question":"Which company owns Java?",
        "Choice1":"Apple",
        "Choice2":"Microsoft",
        "Choice3":"Oracle",
        "Answer":"3"
    }
    ,
    {
        "Question":"How do you print a new line in Java?",
        "Choice1":"System.out.print()",
        "Choice2":"System.out.println()",
        "Choice3":"Output.println()",
        "Answer":"2"
    }
    ,
    {
        "Question":"How do you comment in Java?",
        "Choice1":"//",
        "Choice2":"!",
        "Choice3":"Comment:",
        "Answer":"1"
    }
    ,
    {
        "Question":"How do you store text?",
        "Choice1":"String",
        "Choice2":"int",
        "Choice3":"double",
        "Answer":"1"
    }
    ,
    {
        "Question":"Which would you use to store the number 3.25?",
        "Choice1":"int",
        "Choice2":"double",
        "Choice3":"boolean",
        "Answer":"2"
    }
    ,
    {
        "Question":"How do you initialize the variable num that equals 10?",
        "Choice1":"int num = 10",
        "Choice2":"String num = 10",
        "Choice3":"num = 10",
        "Answer":"1"
    }
    ,
    {
        "Question":"Which operator compares?",
        "Choice1":"==",
        "Choice2":"=",
        "Choice3":"Compare()",
        "Answer":"1"
    }
    ,
    {
        "Question":"How do you create a method?",
        "Choice1":"method[]",
        "Choice2":"method:",
        "Choice3":"method()",
        "Answer":"3"
    }
    ,
    {
        "Question":"What word is used to make a class?",
        "Choice1":"class",
        "Choice2":"class()",
        "Choice3":"NewClass",
        "Answer":"1"
    }
    ,
    {
        "Question":"How do you multiply in Java?",
        "Choice1":"%",
        "Choice2":"*",
        "Choice3":"x",
        "Answer":"2"
    }
    ,
    {
        "Question":"How do you import a package?",
        "Choice1":"package",
        "Choice2":"git clone",
        "Choice3":"import",
        "Answer":"3"
    }
]
